<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="copyright">
        /*
 * Copyright © 2023 Insula Institute for Integrative Therapy Research, Hannover &amp; Bielefeld University
 * Copyright © 2023 Evgenii Pustozerov, Florian Beissner
 * Copyright © 2018 Till-Ansgar Neubert, Jorge Manuel Sánchez
 * Copyright © 2014-2016 Hannover Medical School
 * Copyright © 2014 Tawfik Moher Alsady, Florian Beissner
 *
 * SMaRT is scientific research software. It is not a medical device and should not be considered as such.
 * It does not provide medical advice or diagnoses and is not intended to replace professional medical advice,
 * diagnosis, or treatment. Users should always seek the advice of a doctor or other qualified health provider
 * with any questions they may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice
 * or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this app. It is the sole responsibility of the
 * user to verify the regulatory requirements for the intended use of the program and to comply with all regulatory
 * requirements required by the applicable laws governing its use. The provision of information through this app
 * does not imply a doctor-patient relationship and should not be construed as such. By downloading and/or using
 * this app or source code, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this disclaimer and agree to be bound by its terms.
 *
 * SMaRT uses the Hannover Body Template from Till-Ansgar Neubert &amp; Florian Beissner (2019). Hannover Body Template.
 * figshare. Dataset. https://doi.org/10.6084/m9.figshare.7637387 under CC BY 4.0 (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)
 *
 * This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 * it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 * the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 * (at your option) any later version.
 *
 * This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 * but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
 * GNU General Public License for more details.
 *
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 * along with this program.
 */

    </string>
</resources>